<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Servers>

	<ServerGroup Name="Ravenhearst">
	
		<Server Name="Ravenhearst 10">
			<Description>
			Stable release of Ravenhearst for 1.1b14. Currently on v10.1.0b13
			
			Future v10 updates will automatically post here. Title will not change. These include both client and server files. For direct files head to our discord.
			
			The ORIGINAL Hardcore mod from A14 brings its mixture of slower grind and difficulty to A20 with more features and changes than ever before!
			
			Do you enjoy a more methodical and slower based progression system? Do you feel the base game is too fast, other mods seem uneven or just not catering to that specific hardcore taste that you want?
			
			Ravenhearst is the mod for you! Featuring hundreds of balancing changes and tweaks, new recipes, new deco, new enemies like Night Terrors, new vehicles, Tier 5 radiated pois, Journal Quest line with end game rewards, expanded EVERYTHING, Learn by Doing, old restored vanilla features like upgrades to blocks, and hundreds of more features and changes Ravenhears has enough fright and terror to satisfy even the most toughest of players.</Description>
		
			Patch Notes for 10.1.0b13
						
				Adjusted Menu Tips
				Planks now made in Table Saw
				Changed Icon On Ravenhearst Challenges
				Fixed Cash Register Hitboxes
				Items can now break if not repaired when they hit 0
				You now receive a Working Toaster when destroying an in world toaster
				Fixed Coffeemaker model offsets
				Complete Armor Stat Rework
				Adjusted Nut and Berry Bush Appearance
				Added Nut and Berry Bush to an additional sub biome of the forest
				Fixed Coffeemaker Vanilla Models
				Fixed Stone and Scrap Shovel and Pickaxe Harvesting Tags
				Added Multiple Car Paint Items
				Added OCB Crooked Deco
				Blood Moons last until dawn after day 14
				Fixed On Screen Day and Date
				Shortened Zombie Reaches
				Recycle Bins now downgrade
				Added Storage Progression
				Added Localization to New Storage Options
				Added New Storage
				Added Cans of Nuts and Berries with better stats you can craft in Campfire with an Empty Can
				More tiles will now spawn on RWG
				Model changed for Barricades
				Barricade health lowered to 150
				Fixed Icon for Taza Stone Pickaxe
				Seeds no longer scrap
				Removed Aluminum from Wasteland
				Removed Coal from Snow
				Fixed Nitrate not spawning in one Snow biome
				Added Dysentery to Moldy Bread
				Adjustments to Outdoor Night Light and Indoor Lighting for a more natural darkness
				Fixed Loading Screen Tip Localization
				Crops give an 80 percent chance of seed back
				Added New Challenges - Yakov
				Added time back to hud
				Seed Packs are now a bundle. Open for random seeds
				Removed seed pack crafting
				Farmer Class now gets schematic for Hoe
				Hoe added to loot
				Removed Grills from loot
				Sap no longer scraps
				Removed Steel and Iron Crates from Craft. Must upgrade Wooden one
				Added Wood Writeable Crate to Progression
				Moved Wood Crafts to Table Saw
				Scrap Axe no longer repairs/upgrades
				Fixed Book Reading Animations
				Removed LOTL bonus from nuts and berries
				Added New Zombies by Double G
				Added Treasures and Trinkets that you can find while digging you can sell to the traders
				Increased Leather made from Hides
				Reduced Craft Time of Dried Jerky
				Increased Brighntess of Survival Campfire, Campfire and Tanning Rack Icons
				Moved Around Vanilla Challenges to make sense for the Basic Journal Quest
				Updated Score
				Fixed nut and berry harvests
				Fixed Tags and Model on Dirty Bandage
				Added Reinforced Repair Kits for Reinforced Tools and Weapons
				Reinforced Tools are now Locked Properly
				Fixed description on Bowl of Honey
				Ammo Loot Rebalance. Less ammo found in the world
				RWG Edits - Towns and cities can now spawn in Forests
				Traders can now spawn roadside in the Wilderness
				Various scope and iron sight tweaks and fixes to better align them
				Extended Old Building Upgrading to include Aluminum and Tungsten Paths
				Added Grass Cutter
				Removed Cardio Perk as it is now integrated into Athletics
				Removed Mother Lode as it is now integrated into Construction and Mining Tools Skills
				Added Version Check to Mod Load - Yakov
				Adjusted Animal Spawning
				Added Sprint Toggling Fix
				Added Startup Optimizer - OCBMaurice
				Added Stop Fuel Waste - OCBMaurice
				Added New Map Waypoint Icons - OCBMaurice
				Adjustments to Interior Lighting
				Adjustments to Night Time Exterior Lighting
				Reduced Amount of XP Given for Harvesting, Repairing and Upgrading Blocks
				Reduced chances of perk and skill books in mailboxes
				Removed Junk Drone from loot
				Added Multiple New Vehicle Mods for Speed, Gas Consumption, Light Intensity
				Commented out Water Valve Block Model making water sounds in POIs
				Added expanded firearms. Most are vanilla values, we will need to adjust them in the future. Schematics to make them can be found in Wasteland and Tier 5 loot crates.
				Added Chance of Hazmat to Military Lockers and Army Trucks
				Adjusted backpack loot in military lockers and laundry
				Removed Sprains and Strains as Splint now heals Sprains
				Gas can no longer be drinkable
				Added Sounds to All Ravenhearst food and water
				Added proper perk bonuses to Ravenhearst medical items
				Added a Supply bundle to the starter kit so you can open the item portion at a later date
				Removed Backpacks except for one type due to way action skill works for backpack
				Updated RH Core - Yakov
				Adjusted Skill Point Rewards for Basic Questline and Challenge Redemption to 5 total down from 8
				Armor Tier Stat Fixes to Match our Quality
				Fixed Armor Display Bug creating False Stat Displays - Redbeard + Yakov
				Updated Active Ingredients - Redbeard
				Fixed Air Drop Crates Not Despawning - Yakov
				Fixed Boiled Water in Cans and Jars crafting in the Stove
				Changed Icon Type on Backpacks
				Removed Unused Craft Skill Books from Loot and Bundles
				Raised Health on All Workstations
				Increased cost to make Lockpicks
				Added Wasteland Lockpick that unlocks Tier 5 and Wasteland Crates. Craftable at Advanced Engineering 5. Lootable where Hazmat is found.
				Added Missing Perk Books to Research Desk (Fireman 7, Mining 7, Heist 3, Hunter Books, Looter Books)
				Lowered Bee Hive Timer to 120 from 180
				Changed Research Desk Ingredient to Office Chair Variant Block
				Fixed Tomato Plant Hitbox
				Vehicle Craft Skill now set to 200. Vehicle unlocks spaced put more
				Mechanic now receives 5 vehicle skill books to craft a bicycle but no bicycle parts and a Wrench
				Removed Buggy Action0 Left Click Actions from Sacks and Buckets
				Increased and balanced HP on later tier building blocks
				Increased resources needed to craft steel and concrete shape blocks
				Increased Price of Water Filter
				Removed Water Filter from craft of Dew Collector
				Waster Filter now gives Murky Water and 1 jar as a mod in Dew Collector. Still doubles speed
				Removed Water Filter from Chef Class
				Adjusted haziness to radiation - Yakov
				Updated pick up sounds for antibiotics, custom vehicles, books and magazines
				Increased Health on trees
				Fixed 1970 Refrigerator Harvest
				Improved Wellness Death Logic - Yakov
				Moved Death Wellness Buff to C# to make it more reliable switching Permadeath on and off - Yakov
				Added Carbon Fiber Crafted
				Added Resin Bottle Crafted
				Added Treasure Maps - CTVI
				Added Scrap Club, Spear and Sledgehammer
				Rebalanced Scrap Tools
				Added improved hordes game option. Off by default. - Yakov
				Added improved hordes to config yaml - Yakov
				Added Pick up Sounds to Repair Kits, Resources, Crops, Medicine, Ores, Bars
				Added Pick up Sounds to Repair Kits, Resources, Crops, Medicine, Ores, Bars
				Updated all of Bdubyah vehicles
				New Onion Plant Asset Added
				Updated Improved Hordes Localization with More Accurate Info - Yakov
				Added Torch Framework from Laydor for Performance, Lighting and Config - Yakov
				Fixed Working Gas and Charcoal Grill Models
				Removed BBQ Grill Food Recipes from Stoves
				Added and Removed Categories Needed and no Longer Needed from Grills and Stoves
				Began Adding Back Vanilla Food Hand Models
				Added More Arcade Machines
				Added Slot Machines - 50,100,500 Denominations to Craft through Final Stand Reward
				Added Arcade Machines to Craft through Final Stand Reward
				Added Berries to Spoilage
				Removed Moldy Bread from Spoiling
				Scrap Weapons Now Repair with Reinforced Repair Kit
				Wood Club Now Requires Primitive Repair Kit
				Removed Scrapping from Primitive Weapons
				Increased Random Chances of Getting Vehicle Part or Skill Books as Random Roll
				Added Frozen Water and Stew to Chef Class heated up in Microwave When Needed
				Added Craftable Freezer
				Added Fridges and Cooler to Electrician Skill
				Forging Tunnel scraps to Iron
				Added Scrollable 63 slot backpack after going insane
				Removed Old Jukebox due to deprecated Asset
				Added Lemon Tree and Lemons. Recipes and Fixes to come
				Added New Dew Collector. Place and Upgraded with 2 Tarp. Wait some time then loot the filled collector. Fix with Tarps again.
				Collapsed Dew Collectors Now have a chance for a water filter and a tarp when harvested
				Fixed sack holdtype for a few items - Yakov
				Fix vanilla issue of zombies dropping loot on despawn. Now only drops loot on kill - Yakov
				Removed Can and Jar of Insects from Spoiling
				Special Enemies will Now Start to Appear after Gamestage 250 on Blood Moons, and in the world after GS 500
				Air Drop Zombies Now run and are tiered to be more difficult and faster as gamestage increases
				Added 2 Bottles of Acid to Mechanic Class
				Tinkered With Spoilage Timers All Around to Last a Bit Longer
				Lockpick Skill Matters. Lockpicking More Difficult and Slower but buying Perks in it Makes it Better
				Added 45 and 556 ammo to ammo lootlists
				Added Water to Trail Mix
				Moved Hazmat Suit Loot to Infested Tier 4 and 5
				Replaced Nude Female Zombie
				Removed Harvestable Corpses for Performance and Balance
				Increased Rotting Flesh and Bones Given from Certain Animals
				Removed Male Nude Zombie
				Doors Now Require a Door Knob to Be repaired
				Cook those eggs boys and girls
				Updated AGFHUD
				Added Preloader - Redbeard
				Added Rain Collector. Works like a Vanilla Dew, unlocked at Workstation 90 gives infected water. For now it does NOT have a filter but it may in next update
				Added Proper Repair Kits to Class Weapon Selections
				Removed Quad Armor Pocket Mod
				Increased Craft Skill to 150-200 depending on the craft skill
				Added a new Attribute Page for Tier 5 Books
				Fixed All Action Skill Buffs (Bleed, KO)
				Removed Incorrect Storages from Advanced Engineering
				Added Painted Storage Boxes to Workstation Skill
				You now get 5 Fertilizer per Craft
				Fixed Fertilizer Sack Descriptions
				Adjusted All Ingredient Counts To Our Action Skill Levels - Jax/Yakov
				Increased Chance of Workstation Skill Magazines in Workbench and Chemistry Station
				Removed Item Variation Rolls for Stats
				Updated tagging on Axes and Tools so the custom Action Skill bonuses are tagged properly
				Stone Hammers are no longer sellable
				Storages can be picked up to tier 4 only. After they will destroy and you will need to make new ones.
				Fridges and Coolers can be Taken via 15 second delays
				Added Throwable Items and Perk
				Reduced Compost needed to make ground fertile from 10 to 7
				Reduced Fertilizer needed to fertilize crop from 5 to 4
				Fixed Bleeding Particle - Yakov
				Removed 200m Limit from Sharing Option - Yakov
				Honeycomb no longer cures Infection
				Reduced Action Skill Mailbox Loot
				Increased Tier 8 Storage to 100 slots
				Tier 8 Storage requires Forged Tungsten
				Added RWG Modifications that will force a spawn of every poi at least once on a map
				Fixed up Tier 7, 8 ,9 Storages so they flow better
				Added some Wilderness Decor
				Fixed Baton Unlock Order
				Building Supply Loot Balance
				Zombie Loot Bag Looting Adjustments
				Added New Supply Pick Ups to Final Stand Satchels and Chests
				Moved Icee to Special Drinks Category in Vending
				Removed Socket tool from Motorcycle Handlebar Craft
				Removed Propane Tank Harvest from Working Grills
				Rain Collector Now Accepts Industrial Grade Tarp Mod to Convert Infected Water to Dirty
				Fixed Tier 5 Painted Loot Container Size
				Increased Health on Night Walkers
				Fixed Loot Container cancel instant looting - Yakov
				Fixed Final Stand Bloodmoon cancelling early - Yakov
				Changed buff duration of questbloodmoon to 8 ingame hours - Yakov
				Removed loot delay from player storage - Yakov
				Fixed inconsistencies in Radios
				Fixed Tags and name of Telescopic Baton to match Proper Perks
				Renamed Pistols Skill to Handguns for Clarity
				Weapons and Tools now have the correct Ingredient Cost Increases in Recipes, including Legendary Parts
				Bow Parts and All Weapon Parts should start showing up in loot
				Concrete and Cobble stacks increased to 500
				Increased Hazmat Chance in Army Trucks
				Added Tool and Weapon Parts to all RH Tools and Weapons
				Fixed Crafting Ingredient Counts from base adds to percent adds to match vanilla increases
				Changed Chromium Ore Texture
				Added Pallets for Carbon, Chromium, Tungsten and Aluminum
				Increased Recipe for Reinforced Chain Link Fencing
				Increased Probability on 44 Ammo
				Added Mods Category to Mechanic Bench
				Added Farmer Set Health Bonuses to all RH food and veggies
				Added Station Pickup Sounds to UI
				Added Bucket Pickup Sounds to UI
				Swapped Icons for Charred Red and White Meats
				Removed Stone Tool Clutter from Traders and Loot
				Removed Spoilage from Can of Berries
				Removed Unneeded Farming Control Panel
				Diggie holes have a range of 5 blocks from water to seed, placing pipes in the water and putting a sprinkler on TOP of the pipe has a 10 meter range! the range is from sprinkler to crops not pipe so keep that in mind.


				Added the Following POIs

				Added Old West Migration POI Set, adds more Old West towns and POIs to tiles and biomes

				Added ZZTongs Prefab Pack which adds over 100 pois, decos and filler stamps for a lively world - ZZTong with edits by Jax

				rh_factoryraid_xtiericee
				rh_forestcamp_xtiericee
				rh_warehouse_xtiericee
				rh_junkyard_xtiericee
				rh_farm_house_Lazy_Turtle
				rh_LakeView_Lazy_Turtle
				rh_LazyCafe_Lazy_Turtle
				rh_LazyFarm_01_Lazy_Turtle
				rh_LazyShops_Lazy_Turtle
				rh_Red_Rocket_Lazy_Turtle
				rh_barricaded_house_1_Officecats5
				rh_Petting_Zoo_FluffyPanda
				rh_Red_Rocket_01_FluffyPanda
				rh_Stus_Zoo_Officecats5
				rh_super_prison_max_Officecats5
				rh_advanced_junkyard_02_Officecats5
				oldwest_store_gun_01
				oldwest_abandoned_house_01
				oldwest_abandoned_house_02
				oldwest_country_junkyard_01
				oldwest_homesteader_01_arramus
				oldwest_mixstrip_01_arramus
				oldwest_25x50_corn_01_arramus
				oldwest_rural_church_01
				rh_TheAfterLife_Duhwolf
				rh_Nuketown2024_Camabis
				rh_airstrip_SurvivorAndy
				rh_ultrascans_clinic_SurvivorAndy
				rh_woodbury_SurvivorAndy
				rh_tesko_supermarket_SurvivorAndy
				rh_malibu_club_SurvivorAndy
				rh_busty_beers_stripclub_SurvivorAndy
				rh_bigbluebox_SurvivorAndy
				rh_take_four_film_studio_SurvivorAndy
				rh_wilderness1_SurvivorAndy
				rh_wilderness2_SurvivorAndy
				rh_wilderness3_SurvivorAndy
				rh_wilderness4_SurvivorAndy
				rh_wilderness5_SurvivorAndy
				rh_Alamo_Level50Unlocked
				rh_Data_Center_Level50Unlocked
				oldwest_cran5000soda_01_arramus
				rh_Cedar_Creek_Officecats5
				rh_Club_Hotel_SG1o9
				rh_Epidemic_Playland_old_SG1o9
				rh_Harold_Fetchkick_Asylum_SG1o9
				oldwest_ekoguns_01_arramus
				oldwest_gas_station_07
				oldwest_gas_station_08
				oldwest_ranger_station_02
				oldwest_remnant_bookshop_business_03
				oldwest_remnant_mill_01
				oldwest_store_book_04
				oldwest_store_grocery_04
				oldwest_store_grocery_05
				oldwest_store_grocery_06
				oldwest_survivor_site_05
				oldwest_apper_01_arramus
				oldwest_meatloaf_01_arramus
				oldwest_ranger_station_02
				oldwest_store_book_04
				oldwest_store_grocery_05
			
			<Version>Latest</Version>
			
			<Author>JaxTeller718</Author>
			<Admin>JaxTeller718</Admin>
			<AdminContact>support@7d2dmodlauncher.org</AdminContact>
			
			<ReleaseNotes>https://7d2dmodlauncher.org</ReleaseNotes>
			
			
			<Discord>https://discord.gg/0uy8OaV8YAMGZKeS</Discord>
			<WebSite>https://646760816277b.site123.me/</WebSite>
			<Twitter>https://twitter.com/JaxTeller718</Twitter>
			<Donate>https://www.paypal.me/FrankCirabisiJr</Donate>
			
			<RemoteReleaseNotes>https://gitlab.com/jaxteller718/ravenhearst_10/-/raw/main/README.md</RemoteReleaseNotes>
			
			
			<Excludes>
				<Exclude>7DaysToDieServer_Data\</Exclude>
			</Excludes>
			<Downloads>
				<Download>https://gitlab.com/jaxteller718/ravenhearst_10</Download>
			</Downloads>
		</Server>
		
	</ServerGroup>
</Servers>
