<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Servers>
	<ServerGroup Name="Silent Hill Mod" Logo="" Description="">
		<Server Name="Silent Hill Mod 1.0" Logo="">
			<Description>
Welcome to Silent Hill Mod For 7 Days To Die
In the fog, fear walks beside you, and death is just a breath away
Features:--
1)The fog covers all the biomes all the time.
2)Screamer Zombie Spawns in the wandering hordes.
3)when you damage the screamer, You have 5 seconds to kill the screamer before she calls the Zombies.
4)There's a big wandering horde spawns every 12-24 hours
5)The fog and wandering hordes start day 2
6)No blood moon hordes
7)Zombies receive 25% extra damage from headshot
8)Higher stacks sizes for ammo, drugs and medical items, resources, and guns parts and throwables
9)Traders and Challenges have been removed
10)Traders pois are open and destructible and their pois are infested with zombies now
11)higher entity spawn rate in biomes
12)You can scrap magazine and every 3 scrapped magazines you can make a different magazine with it
13)96 Backpack Size
14)Copper tools and melee weapons added
15)Copper Ore Added, can be found around the biomes.
16)21 ranged guns added to play with
17)Added Back A19 farming
18)You can craft guns and tools parts in the workbench
19)Supply Drops added
20) Airdrops are protected, that's mean zombies spawn around it
21)New Magazine Added,Launchers Magazine for crafting grenade launchers
22) All tools and weapons has 1-6 mod slots for level 1-6
23) Increased the chance to find cooking pot and cooking Grill in Cupboards and Sinks
24) Added dew collector tools to more loot tables
25) Zombies havehigher loot drop chance. , loot drop last longer
26) Reworked airdrop loot
27) added a way to convert old cash to casino coins
28) You can use your coins to craft flares airdrops


	      </Description>
			<Discord>https://discord.gg/GS3wGQTu6U</Discord>
			
			
			<Version>Latest</Version>

			<Downloads>
				<Download>https://github.com/killerbunny264/Silent-Hill-Mod</Download>
			</Downloads>
		</Server>
	</ServerGroup>
</Servers>