<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Servers>
   <ServerGroup Name="7Days2Mod CompoPack" Logo="http://7days2mod.com/images/mods/7d2d/banner_01_vanilla.jpg" Description="Various mods from users, combined with Magoli's prefab compopack.">
      <Server Name="Vanilla XML" Logo="https://github.com/7days2mod/Vanilla/blob/master/Banner.png?raw=true">
         <Description>Vanilla XML Files with Magoli's CompoPack
This includes a copy of the vanilla XML files.</Description>
         <RSS>https://github.com/7days2mod/Vanilla/commits/master.atom</RSS>
         <ReleaseNotes>https://github.com/7days2mod/Vanilla</ReleaseNotes>
         <Downloads>
            <Download>https://github.com/7days2mod/Vanilla/archive/master.zip</Download>
            <Download>https://github.com/7days2mod/Compo/archive/master.zip</Download>
         </Downloads>
      </Server>
      <Server Name="Unofficial XML Fixes" Logo="https://github.com/7days2mod/7-Days-to-die-Unofficial-XML-Fixes/blob/master/Banner.png?raw=true">
         <Description>A collection of unofficial XML Fixes by the Community with Magoli's CompoPack</Description>
         <RSS>https://github.com/7days2mod/7-Days-to-die-Unofficial-XML-Fixes/commits/master.atom</RSS>
         <ReleaseNotes>https://github.com/7days2mod/7-Days-to-die-Unofficial-XML-Fixes</ReleaseNotes>
         <Downloads>
            <Download>https://github.com/7days2mod/7-Days-to-die-Unofficial-XML-Fixes/archive/master.zip</Download>
            <Download>https://github.com/7days2mod/Compo/archive/master.zip</Download>
         </Downloads>
      </Server>
  
      <Server Name="Valmod Classic Horde Survival" Logo="https://github.com/7days2mod/Classic-Horde-Survival/blob/master/Banner.png?raw=true">
         <Description>Valmar's Classic Horde Survival Mod with Magoli's CompoPack
 Welcome to CHS - Classic Horde Survival. This mod aims to offer a completely different experience from vanilla. If you want a mod that adds more farming, crafting, building or expands the game to last for hundreds of days this is NOT the mod for you. This mod is intended to be more towards having a few hours of fun in a horde mode rather than spending weeks building cities. If you just want to kill hordes of zombies while scavenging for food and ammo, this mod might be for you.

Warning: If you have a below average computer you may experience FPS issues when playing this mod due to the large number of zombie spawns. You can lower your games spawn settings in the game options to try to dial it back some but your millage may vary.</Description>
         <RSS>https://github.com/7days2mod/Classic-Horde-Survival/commits/master.atom</RSS>
         <ReleaseNotes>https://github.com/7days2mod/Classic-Horde-Survival</ReleaseNotes>
         <Downloads>
            <Download>https://github.com/7days2mod/Classic-Horde-Survival/archive/master.zip</Download>
            <Download>https://github.com/7days2mod/Compo/archive/master.zip</Download>
         </Downloads>
      </Server>
      <Server Name="Valmod HORDE Edition" Logo="https://github.com/7days2mod/Valmod-HORDE-EDITION/blob/master/Banner.png?raw=true">
         <Description>Valmar's Horde Edition
More zombies, and headshots to kill!
This is a relatively large mod pack I've gradually created over time. It's mainly a collaboration of all my smaller mods placed together into one larger file.
The Overhaul pack adds the same items and content to the game as the expansion with the key difference being that unlike the expansion the overhaul, as the name implies overhauls some basic aspects of the game. Mainly the recipe system is considerably locked down compared to vanilla. The overhaul is intended for those who want a new experience from the game.
 </Description>
         <RSS>https://github.com/7days2mod/Valmod-HORDE-EDITION/commits/master.atom</RSS>
         <ReleaseNotes>https://github.com/LordValmar/Valmar-HORDE-EDITION</ReleaseNotes>
         <Downloads>
			<Download>https://github.com/7days2mod/Valmod-Overhaul/archive/master.zip</Download>
            <Download>https://github.com/LordValmar/Valmod-HORDE-EDITION/archive/master.zip</Download>
            <Download>https://github.com/7days2mod/Compo/archive/master.zip</Download>
			
         </Downloads>
      </Server>
	  
	  
      <!-- Server Name="True Survival" Logo="https://github.com/7days2mod/True-Survival/blob/master/Banner.png?raw=true">
         <Description>True Survival Mod with Magoli's CompoPack
Modded for more challenging survival combined with a steady slow progression in building and crafting.</Description>
         <RSS>https://github.com/7days2mod/True-Survival/commits/master.atom</RSS>
         <ReleaseNotes>https://github.com/7days2mod/True-Survival</ReleaseNotes>
         <Downloads>
            <Download>https://github.com/7days2mod/True-Survival/archive/master.zip</Download>
            <Download>https://github.com/7days2mod/Compo/archive/master.zip</Download>
         </Downloads>
      </Server-->
	  
      <Server Name="Craftworx" Logo="https://github.com/LatheosMod/Craftworx/blob/master/Banner.png?raw=true">
         <Description>Craftworx
This is a complete overhaul of LathMod, which itself was an overhaul mod for 7 Days to Die. Craftworx is aimed more at folks who enjoy crafting, which means that the crafting skills are more defined than vanilla. Harvesting wood now falls under the Carpentry skill, rather than mining, as do crafting most wood objects in the game. Bows, crossbows, arrows and bolts are now crafted in the Fletching skill, rather than Weapon Smithing. There are also perks and skills which add more ammunition, allow crafting of different kinds of clothing, and more.

Advancing in crafting takes a bit longer than in vanilla, as the skill levels for concrete, steel, and Advanced Tooling (which replaces workbench and also locks the forge) have been raised from vanilla levels. Craftworx adds suppressed firearms, iron bows and crossbows, and a few other new weapons, as well as new weapons perks.

Craftworx features a custom HUD created by Sirillion (with minor modifications), Stallionsden's Backpack Expansion, Valmar's Expanded Traps (modified), a flamethrower from Andy of Andy's Mods (originally for A12 but updated to A15), and SylenThunder's Lighted Glass Blocks (updated from A13). Credit for those parts of this mod goes to them. Additionally, Valmar and StompyNZ were extremely helpful in getting parts of this mod working properly. Thanks, guys!
		</Description>
         <RSS>https://github.com/LatheosMod/Craftworx/commits/master.atom</RSS>
         <ReleaseNotes>https://7daystodie.com/forums/showthread.php?54652-Craftworx</ReleaseNotes>
         <Downloads>
            <Download>https://github.com/LatheosMod/Craftworx/archive/master.zip</Download>
			<Download>https://github.com/7days2mod/Compo/archive/master.zip</Download>
         </Downloads>
      </Server>

	  
         <Server Name="A Clockwork Project" Logo="https://github.com/ClockworkOrange420/A-Clockwork-Project/blob/master/Banner.png?raw=true">
         <Description>A Clockwork Project Mod for Alpha 14.4
This mod is designed to perfectly balance all aspects of the game from Progression to Loot and Crafting!</Description>
         <RSS>https://github.com/ClockworkOrange420/A-Clockwork-Project/commits/master.atom</RSS>
         <ReleaseNotes>https://github.com/ClockworkOrange420/A-Clockwork-Project/</ReleaseNotes>
         <Downloads>
            <Download>https://github.com/ClockworkOrange420/A-Clockwork-Project/archive/master.zip</Download>
			<Download>https://github.com/7days2mod/Compo/archive/master.zip</Download>
         </Downloads>
      </Server>
   </ServerGroup>

	  
</Servers>
