<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Servers>
    <ServerGroup Name="Destroyer of Dreams" Logo="" Description="Can you escape the Destoyer?">
        <Server Name="Destroyer of Dreams" Logo="">
            <Description>
				A mini overhaul mod for Release Ver. 2.0(b295)

				This mod pack was created for a solo or multiplayer challenge onboard an US Arleigh Burke Class Destroyer DG-51, Concept design by CannonFodder83 and redesigned by Devilskut for Release
				Ver. 2.0(b295) with code help from Techgeek_20 and "bug hunting" from AngelacusGaming.

				Notes about this mini-mod:

				Zombie corpses now drop an entity-specific red loot bag.
				Removed non-essential vehicle parts from loot and crafting.
				Beds, Bedrolls, and land claim block recipes removed.
				Removed treasure maps from loot.
				Acid can now be made in the campfire, but a beaker is a required tool. Can also be crafted cheaper in the chem station. Unlocked with Grease Monkey 4.
				Mod-specific loading screen tips.
				Localization tweaks (names of those that have tested and completed the challenge).
				Perk books can now drop from zombies along with magazines. The chance of a perk book increases with the relevant perk points spent, just like skill magazines.
				Loot tables adjusted accordingly, so certain zombies have a chance to drop certain perk books, just like skill magazines.
				Removed Better Barter, Daring Adventurer and Charismatic Nature from the intellect skill tree.
				Number of Dukes/old cash from Businessman/Party Girl is increased, probability increased from 10% to 20%.
				Slight increase in oil shale from cement mixer loot.
				Increased chance of antibiotics from nurses per perk point spent in Physician, up to a max chance of 35%.
				Base chance of skill magazines from radiated zombies increased from 10% to 13%.
				Changed the quest requirements for gathering UH-60  parts to reflect maxed-out Grease Monkey (removed a possible soft-lock)
				Antibiotics loot probability from nurses now tied to Physician perk.
				Player placed workstations can be picked up with no need for a land claim block. (Workstation MUST be empty of all tools, items, and materials for this to work)

				THE DESTROYER OF DREAMS CHALLENGE:
				Can you survive long enough to liberate the zombie threat and complete your mission using nothing but what you can scavenge from the Destroyer and local Docks.?

				This challenge brings you back as a lone hard core survivor, or in a group of seasoned specialists of the AIRCRAFT CARRIER CHALLENGE on a reinfested Destroyer in dry docks for repairs.

				Your only means of completing your mission is to gather everything you need to be able to craft an UH-60 Helicopter to reach your final objectives.

				A mini overhaul mod for Ver. 2.0(b295) . Designed for group or solo play with an Arleigh Burke Class Destroyer DG-51, a Guns Trader and a mission to liberate the zombie threat once and for all.

				Five (5) custom worlds, one for each biome, so you can choose your starting "difficulty" - Forest, Burnt, Desert, Snow, or the ultimate challenge, Wasteland.

				Custom-edited POI'S, giving you everything you need to be able to complete your quests.

				Custom questline, guiding you on your way.

				CHALLENGE RULES:

				1: You must survive until you are able to build an UH-60 Helicopter, fly off and complete your final mission.

				2: The rubble on the ground around the DOCKS is NOT part of the Destroyer, and as such may NOT be used to support any structures, or to grow any crops,
				unless you can do this WITHOUT touching it.

				3: You may build bridges off the Docks to reach things, but those bridges must support themselves and cannot touch the ground.

				4: You may NOT mine or dig under the Destroyer or the Docks.

				5: All default game settings, unless you want to turn up the difficulty. It's recommended to have respawns set to 5 days groups and 7 days solo and turn airdrops OFF.

				6: If you or anyone in your party dies, your mission is over, however you may choose continue to complete your mission.

				Contributors:
				DishongLootBags 						-Author: w00kien00kie
				DishongPickupWorkstations 				-Author: w00kien00kie
				WMMLootRespawnTweak				        -Author: w00kien00kie

				Custom Poi's by Cannon_Fodder83 and Devilskut.

				Additional thanks for permission to use following modlets by their respective creator(s):

				Khelldon Custom Menu 					-Author: Khelldon
				Military Blocks							-Author: Cannon_Fodder83,Shrader971
				0-Score								    -Author: Spherii
				UH-60 Helicopter                        -Author: Bdubyah
				AircraftcarrierGuns						-Author: Killerbunny264

				Shout outs and thanks to the mod authors and Hells_Janitor for the Dishong Tower Challenge and allowing usage of their mods and code.
				Shout outs and thanks to the mod authors, Special CPB Blocks permission by StallionsDen CP Team, SarahAndJeff, TFP, Specter(to Sarahandjeff).

				For full details, check the forum post here: *No post*

				Found a bug or poi stability issue and wish to let us know?  Head to https://github.com/Devilskut/Destroyer_of_Dreams_High_Seas/issues and open an issues ticket.

			</Description>
            <Version>2.0</Version>
            <EAC>Disabled</EAC>
			<Discord>https://discord.gg/ePNGymJ3bP</Discord>
			<Donate></Donate>
            <DownloadMode>Clone</DownloadMode>
            <Downloads>
                <Download>https://github.com/Devilskut/Destroyer_of_Dreams_High_Seas.git</Download>
            </Downloads>
        </Server>
    </ServerGroup>
</Servers>
