<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Servers>
	<ServerGroup Name="Zombiedayz" Logo="" Description="">
		<Server Name="Zombiedayz - stable" Logo="">
			<Description>
Zombiedayz A20 is a project by DeftChimp and Sechsterversuch
Modding:Sechsterversuch,Renevandoll,WoodWeevil,Saxe,Zeeeeeeniiiiiii

Other mods are owned that I list here and will remain with them.
We have permission to publish the mods. We don't make any money with it.
The request that we are allowed to use the mods was approved by a confirmation in the chat / mail.
Or do not need any written inquiries, but rather is in the terms of use.

License and Terms of Use

1) You are free to download these files and play them in single player. You can also upload these files to a server,
   to play online provided you have a legal copy of the game (7 Days To Die)

2) You are NOT permitted to change a code, rename or redistribute a model.

3) You are free to customize your experience by modifying the XML files. If you are hosting a server or a game
   with such changed content, you are NOT permitted to pass these changes on without my express permission.
   You MUST get my permission prior to any files, code, models, or assets included in my mods
   which are not shared on your PC or on a dedicated server for private use.

4) Users are NOT allowed to take the code from this mod in order to add it to another mod in any way,
   without asking me beforehand. This also applies to the removal of (parts of) the code, XML or assets as well as changed versions thereof.
   
5) This version of the mod is especially for the modPack (the overhaul) ZombieDayz by ğ•¾ğ–Šğ–ˆğ–ğ–˜ğ–™ğ–Šğ–—ğ–›ğ–Šğ–—ğ–˜ğ–šğ–ˆğ– (Discord: https://discord.gg/X72gTTV).
   It may only be passed on as part of this modPack / Overhaul. As part of this modPack / Overhaul it is allowed
   can be changed and adapted indefinitely as long as the following listed files remain unchanged:
- EN_License_Information.md
- EN_Readme.md
- GER_License_Information.md
- GER_Readme.md
- mod.xml
- ModInfo.xml
- Contact_info.md

All rights reserved, 2022 zombiedayz website: https://www.zombiedayz.info/
Discord: https://discord.gg/X72gTTV

All names listed here are Discord names or a forum / portal

A big thank you to those who supported us.

Zeeeeeeniiiiiii,Unamea

Test team:Test team:Geckomander,HuntingJudy,LichtKaiserin,Luisberd / Sascha,Muddi,Unamea,Gucky81,LadyTauri,sleepcap_mike

A big thank you goes to the modders we are allowed to use the mods or some of them. Or in cooperation.

Bdubyah
JaxTeller718
Guppycur
Gyancher2
Khain
Sirillon
Stallionsden (Valmar)
Stasis
Snufkin
Telrics
Wolfbain 5
Xyth
Riles
bdubyah
Polyman
Lichti
Ragsy
Robeloto


			</Description>
				<Version>Latest</Version>
			<RSS/>
			<Discord>https://discord.gg/X72gTTV</Discord>
				<Excludes>
				<Exclude>7DaysToDieServer_Data\</Exclude>
				<Exclude>\obj\</Exclude>
				<Exclude>\bin\</Exclude>
			</Excludes>
			<ReleaseNotes/>
			<DownloadMode>Clone</DownloadMode>
			<Downloads>
				<Download>https://dev.azure.com/DeftCHIMP/_git/Zombiedayz-A20</Download>
			</Downloads>
		</Server>
		
		

	</ServerGroup>

</Servers>
