<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Servers>
    <ServerGroup Name="28 Alphas Later" Logo="https://media.discordapp.net/attachments/1155647724478275614/1180961617417085000/background.png" Description="Will you survive?">
        <Server Name="28 Alphas Later" Logo="https://media.discordapp.net/attachments/1155647724478275614/1180961617417085000/background.png">
            <Description>*** 28 Alphas Later ***

The idea behind this mod is to slow progression, make traders less powerful, and generally extend the time for a playthrough, while keeping the vanilla look and feel.

*** FEATURES *** 

*** STARTER ITEMS ***

"Starter" items are now in a backpack, found in slot 2 of your toolbelt. Open it with your primary action (LMB by default on PC)
When you open the backpack, read the note from The Duke to obtain your starter weapon of choice.
The starter quest is now just "place bedroll", which you'll receive on opening the starter backpack.

*** GENERAL GAMEPLAY ***

Player is permanently infected, and the infection persists through death. There is a cure, but you’ll need to read a lot of medical magazines to learn how to make it.
Headshots ONLY. Zombies can only be damaged/killed with headshots, or with fire, or with explosives.
Zombies DON'T bleed. Nothing undead takes bleed damage.
Hazmat zombies are a guaranteed source of hazmat gear. Kill one, and if it drops loot, it'll have some hazmat gear in there.
There are more zombies in the world. Biomes are gamestaged, which means zombies get tougher and their number increases as you level up.
Zombies are tougher.
Nights are dangerous, downtown is much more dangerous.
Traders are still protected, but they open from dawn 'til dusk. No more waiting for 6 am anymore.
Traders and vending machines are MUCH more expensive to buy from, and will buy from you at a much lower price.
Crafting is 25% more expensive, and loot, harvesting and scrapping quantities are much lower.
XP required to level increased by 25%.
Dismember chance lowered to 1% per attribute level, max at 10%.
Knife base damage rebalanced to account for the lack of bleeding zombies.
60-slot backpack

*** AMMO, WEAPONS, MODS AND ARMOUR ***

New basic wood arrow/bolt. Made from a single branch, its range is poor, its damage isn't great, and it always breaks on impact.
All arrows and bolts have a 25% chance of causing bleeding on a living target. Shame it doesn't work on the undead ...
The serrated blade only fits on spears and knuckles now.
Hazmat armour mods can be crafted from hazmat gear. You’ll still need all five mods (head, gloves, chest, legs, and boots) for full radiation protection.
New mods - blessed metal for stopping mutated regen. NiCd is back, as is Flaming Oil and Liquid Nitrogen.
New clothing mod - cycling shorts. Install them in your leg armour/clothing and save 25% stamina when cycling.

*** BLOCKS/WORKSTATIONS ***

The beehive. Find bees (and honey) in specific tree stumps (beehives) in the world, and use them to produce honey. Normal wild tree stumps have a higher chance of giving honey too.
The dew collector now uses a filter WITH durability. It has to be replaced when it breaks, or the collector will stop.
The chicken snare. Place this block down, and load it with corn seed to attract and trap chickens, which can be used in coops to produce eggs.
The chicken coop. Place this block, add a chicken from a trap, and it will produce eggs over time. The chicken will "dry out" over time, and will need replacing to keep producing eggs.
The tablesaw cannot be crafted, it can only be collected from POIs. Press "E" to pick one up.
The workbench now has slots for a wrench, hammer, ratchet, impact driver, and nail gun. These tools are needed to craft a lot of items, and some items have been moved from inventory crafting to workbench crafting.
The cement mixer now requires gasoline to work.
The forge no longer requires you to smelt items. You can use the items directly from your inventory.

*** BUFFS/DEBUFFS ***

Snakes and Spider zombies will envenom you when they attack. Kill snakes to extract its venom, which can be used to make antivenom.
The Wasteland biome is irradiated, and very, VERY dangerous. You'll need a hazmat suit before you venture in there.
Radiated zombies now irradiate the player when they attack. A full hazmat suit or a full set of hazmat mods negates this.
Burnt zombies now set the player on fire when they attack. A full hazmat suit or a full set of hazmat mods negates this.
Honey infection treatment reduced to 3% from 5%.

*** ZOMBIES/ENEMIES ***

Bears and wolves are back in the forest.
Zombie health increases with game difficulty. Scavenger starts with zombies dealing 100% damage and no health bonus. Zombie health increases by 20% per level, up to 100% more health on insane difficulty. Damage received by zombies increases by 25% per level up to Survivalist, and then a further 50% jump to Insane (150% more damage dealt at maximum difficulty)
Hazmat zombies are now immune to burning.
New Mutated zombie variant. Bigger, tankier, stronger, yellower, and with more radiated regen. You'll need a blessed metal mod to take them down - the wasteland is full of these guys.
New Frozen zombie variant. Slightly tougher, slightly slower, slightly more XP, and take slightly more damage than their “Normal” counterparts. Immune to the effects of liquid nitrogen, and if they touch you, your movement is reduced by 25%. You can negate this by maxing out the Well Insulated perk.  Found in the snow biome.
New Rotting zombie variant. They have lower HP, lower XP reward, and they take more damage. Found in the forest and desert biomes.
Normal, frozen and rotting 'Fat' zombies (Big Mama, tourist) don’t puke, but they do explode …

*** FOOD/FARMING ***

All canned food found in loot, vending machines, and trader stock is "uncooked". Cook it to make it safe to eat, or eat it and run the risk of food poisoning ...
Uncooked cans don't replenish health, just food and water.
Three new recipes - Chicken stew and chicken miso, top of the tier 4 food chain, and Scrambled Eggs, basic recipe, unlocked by default. Needs a cooking pot, but is a better use for eggs.
MegaCrush is craftable, in a campfire, with a beaker, and cheaper in a chemistry station.
Pies and cheesecake need honey for that sweet, sweet taste now.
Crops' growing time is double that of vanilla.

*** PROGRESSION ***

There is no more Daring Adventurer or Better Barter. Traders will give a drink after every quest tier, which will increase bartering by 5% and trader level by one for each tier of quests completed. MAKE SURE YOU HAVE SPACE IN YOUR INVENTORY FOR IT!!
There is a new perk, Survival Instinct. It's a "single-player" version of Charismatic Nature. 5 levels, each level gains you an addtional 5 health/stamina, 10% block damage, 5% entity damage, 3% XP, and carry capacity increases by 1.
Living off the Land now offers a discount to crops needed to make seeds, level 2 costs 4 crops per seed, level 3 costs 3 crops per seed.

*** RESOURCES ***

Trees no longer give wood, they give wood logs, scraps, and branches. Logs can be placed and then chopped with an axe for wood, or use the table saw to do it quicker and better.
Primitive weapons and ammo are now made from wood scraps, branches, plant fibres, and/or stone.
Cobblestone is now more expensive to make in your inventory. Use a cement mixer to make it cheaper.
Concrete now requires a bucket of water and is crafted in batches of 250.
Repair kits are more expensive, and weapons/armour/tools that require specific crafting parts now require a specific repair kit.

*** VEHICLES ***

All vehicles EXCEPT the bicycle are too heavy for you to carry.
Vehicles CANNNOT be used underwater.



Contributors:

Particle systems/Unity edits 			-Author: redbeardt

Original Chicken Coop model 			-Author: DocRabbit

HJPlayerItemCount						-Author: w00kien00kie

IDCAdvancedDewCollector 				-Author: I Don't Care

IDCAnimalSnare							-Author: I Don't Care

IDCBeehive								-Author: I Don't Care

IDCCore									-Author: I Don't Care

KHA21-HPBars							-Author: Khaine

60-slot backpack (xml code)				-Author: Khaine

Khelldon Custom Menu 					-Author: Khelldon

Custom Menu Music						-Author: Khaine

Material Modifier 						-Author: Zilox

ColoredContainerStates					-Author: Scomar	

WMMPersistGameOptions					-Author: w00kien00kie

WMMStaminaDehydrationFix				-Author: w00kien00kie

WMMStashBackpack						-Author: w00kien00kie

CustomDifficulty						-Author: Mythix
						
also a huge thank you to Frantic_Dan and redbeardt for the custom HUD base code, main menu localization changes, and to YubiNashi and Frantic_Dan for ideas/balancing and playtesting.
			
            </Description>
            <Discord></Discord>
            <Donate></Donate>
            <EAC>Disabled</EAC>
            <Version>Latest</Version>
            <DownloadMode>Clone</DownloadMode>
            <Downloads>
                <Download>https://github.com/HellsJanitor/28-Alphas-Later</Download>
            </Downloads>
        </Server>
    </ServerGroup>
</Servers>