<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Servers>
	<ServerGroup Name="DianddraD" Logo="" Description="">
		<Server Name="Fear The Night" Logo="">
			<Description>Fear The Night (with Simple UI and Magoli CompoPack) is a mod where the zombies mostly come out at night (pretty much EVERY night), and sleep in the day. Expect there to be a lot of zombies. Zombies drop coin for you to spend. Prepare your base because the zombies are going to WRECK it. Pray you survive the night!

You can still grind for resources if you want, but this mod makes it possible to skip the grind by earning money killing zombies and spending it for what you need to build your base. Players are given a special vending machine that sells resources and gear upon completion of a quest. (as of version 1.0)
			</Description>

			<Version>Latest</Version>
			<ReleaseNotes>https://7daystodie.com/forums/showthread.php?82038-Fear-The-Night-Mod</ReleaseNotes>
			<Downloads>
				<Download>https://github.com/dianddra/Fear-The-Night/archive/master.zip</Download>
			</Downloads>
		</Server>

		<Server Name="Fear The Night Bigger Back Pack" Logo="">
			<Description>Fear The Night (with Simple UI, Magoli CompoPack, and Bigger Backpack) is a mod where the zombies mostly come out at night (pretty much EVERY night), and sleep in the day. Expect there to be a lot of zombies. Zombies drop coin for you to spend. Prepare your base because the zombies are going to WRECK it. Pray you survive the night!

You can still grind for resources if you want, but this mod makes it possible to skip the grind by earning money killing zombies and spending it for what you need to build your base. Players are given a special vending machine that sells resources and gear upon completion of a quest. (as of version 1.0)</Description>
			<Version>Latest</Version>
			<Excludes>
				<Exclude>7DaysToDieServer_Data</Exclude>
			</Excludes>

			<ReleaseNotes>https://7daystodie.com/forums/showthread.php?82038-Fear-The-Night-Mod</ReleaseNotes>
			<Downloads>
				<Download>https://github.com/dianddra/Fear-The-Night-with-Bigger-Backpack/archive/master.zip</Download>
			</Downloads>
		</Server>

		<Server Name="Fear The Night Nomad" Logo="">
			<Description>7 Days To Die Mod Fear The Night goes Nomad! No more landclaim block and vending machine, now you can go anywhere and the Zombies will come at night to get you. Roam around the world on your Mini-Bike and explore Magoli's CompoPack. Take shelter at night and hope you survive the Horde. You start with a mini bike but no coins. Kill Zombies to get coin to spend at Traders. No more grinding for materials when you can buy what you need. Beware! You can get irradiated cops on day one, so FEAR THE NIGHT!
			</Description>
			<Excludes>
				<Exclude>7DaysToDieServer_Data</Exclude>
			</Excludes>
			<Version>Latest</Version>
			<ReleaseNotes>https://7daystodie.com/forums/showthread.php?82038-Fear-The-Night-Mod</ReleaseNotes>
			<Downloads>
				<Download>https://github.com/dianddra/Fear-The-Night-Nomad/archive/master.zip</Download>
			</Downloads>
		</Server>

		<Server Name="The Dead Will Rise" Logo="">
			<Description>The Dead Will Rise, a 7 Days To Die Mod. Similar to Fear The Night mod, but zombies will come anytime day or night that you use a campfire, forge, or chemistry station. Kill Zombies to get coin to spend at Traders. No more grinding for materials when you can buy what you need. Beware! You can get irradiated cops on day one, because The Dead Will Rise!
			</Description>
			<Excludes>
				<Exclude>7DaysToDieServer_Data</Exclude>
			</Excludes>
			<Version>Latest</Version>
			<ReleaseNotes>https://7daystodie.com/forums/showthread.php?82038-Fear-The-Night-Mod</ReleaseNotes>
			<Downloads>
				<Download>https://github.com/dianddra/The-Dead-Will-Rise/archive/master.zip</Download>
			</Downloads>
		</Server>
	</ServerGroup>
</Servers>


